{
    "subject": "resource/RuPaul",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Actor",
    "human_readable": "RuPaul's occupation is Actor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9088422060012817,
            "question": "Is RuPaul known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8478713631629944,
            "question": "What is RuPaul's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8229511976242065,
            "question": "What type of roles has RuPaul played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7528823614120483,
            "question": "Can you name some of RuPaul's most famous acting roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7417618632316589,
            "question": "How long has RuPaul been working as an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7173165082931519,
            "question": "Besides acting, what else is RuPaul famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7101019620895386,
            "question": "Has RuPaul received any awards for their acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6781383752822876,
            "question": "What other talents does RuPaul possess besides acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5719782710075378,
            "question": "What is RuPaul's impact on the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5201582312583923,
            "question": "Are there any notable movies or TV shows featuring RuPaul?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=RuPaul's occupation is Actor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7652_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is RuPaul's impact on the entertainment industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7652_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other talents does RuPaul possess besides acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7652_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has RuPaul received any awards for their acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7652_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7652_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention RuPaul as an actor, stating that he has appeared in over 50 films and television shows both in and out of drag. Additionally, it mentions his roles in specific TV shows and movies, such as \"Crooklyn\" (1994), \"The Brady Bunch Movie\" (1995), and \"AJ & The Queen\" (2020). Therefore, the information supports the triple that RuPaul's occupation is Actor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports RuPaul's occupations as an actor, model, singer, songwriter, television personality, and author. Therefore, the statement \"RuPaul's occupation is Actor\" can be considered correct based on the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}